{
  "response_code": 0,
  "results": [
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "In the anime Initial D, how does Takumi Fujiwara describe a drift?",
      "correct_answer": "'. . . the front tires slide so the car won't face the inside'",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "'. . . the wheels lose traction, making the car slide sideways'",
        "'. . . the car oversteers through a curve, causing it to turn faster'",
        "'. . . you turn a lot'"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "In the anime, Full Metal Panic!, who is Kaname's best friend?",
      "correct_answer": "Kyoko Tokiwa",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Melissa Mao",
        "Ren Mikihara",
        "Teletha 'Tessa' Testarossa"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "In 'Highschool of the Dead', where did Komuro and Saeko establish to meet after the bus explosion?",
      "correct_answer": "Eastern Police Station",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "The Center Mall",
        "Komuro's House",
        "On The Main Bridge"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "Which of the following countries does 'JoJo's Bizarre Adventure: Stardust Crusaders' not take place in?",
      "correct_answer": "Philippines",
      "incorrect_answers": ["India", "Pakistan", "Egypt"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "What year was 'JoJo's Bizarre Adventure: Phantom Blood' first released?",
      "correct_answer": "1987",
      "incorrect_answers": ["2013", "1983", "1995"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "What is the last line muttered in the anime film 'The End of Evangelion'?",
      "correct_answer": "'How disgusting.'",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "'Idiot, I won't let you kill me!'",
        "'Nothing.'",
        "'Goddammit, Shinji.'"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "Winch of these names are not a character of JoJo's Bizarre Adventure?",
      "correct_answer": "JoJo Kikasu",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Jean-Pierre Polnareff",
        "George Joestar",
        "Risotto Nero"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "Which of these anime have over 7,500 episodes?",
      "correct_answer": "Sazae-san",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Naruto", "One Piece", "Chibi Maruko-chan"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "Which song was the callsign for Stefan Verdemann's KWFM radio station in Urasawa Naoki's 'Monster'?",
      "correct_answer": "Over the Rainbow",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "What a Wonderful World",
        "When You Wish Upon A Star",
        "Singing In The Rain"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "Medaka Kurokami from 'Medaka Box' has what abnormality?",
      "correct_answer": "The End",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Perfection", "Sandbox", "Fairness"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "Akatsuki's subclass in 'Log Horizon' is what?",
      "correct_answer": " Tracker",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Assassin", "Scribe", "Apprentice"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "In 'One Piece', who is the girl who overcame her enslaved past and became an agent of an army to fight the corrupt government?",
      "correct_answer": "Koala",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Boa Hancock", "Nico Robin", "Emporio Ivankov "]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "In 'One Piece', what does 'the Pirate King' mean to the captain of the Straw Hat Pirates?",
      "correct_answer": "Freedom",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Promise", "Adventure", "Friendship"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "In 'One Piece', who confirms the existence of the legendary treasure, One Piece?",
      "correct_answer": "Edward 'Whitebeard' Newgate",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Former Marine Fleet Admiral Sengoku",
        "Pirate King Gol D Roger",
        "Silvers Rayleigh"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "Which one of these characters is from 'Legendz : Tale of the Dragon Kings'?",
      "correct_answer": "Shiron",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Jack", "Axia", "Drum"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "In the 'Dragon Ball' franchise, what is the name of Goku's brother?",
      "correct_answer": "Raditz",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Gohan", "Vegeta", "Bardock"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "Which person from 'JoJo's Bizarre Adventure' does NOT house a reference to a band, artist, or song earlier than 1980?",
      "correct_answer": "Giorno Giovanna",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Josuke Higashikata",
        "Jolyne Cujoh",
        "Johnny Joestar"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "In 'Hunter x Hunter', which of the following is NOT a type of Nen aura?",
      "correct_answer": "Restoration",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Emission", "Transmutation", "Specialization"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "In 'Hunter x Hunter', what are members in Killua's family known for being?",
      "correct_answer": "Assassins",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Bandits", "Hunters", "Ninjas"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "The 'To Love-Ru' Manga was started in what year?",
      "correct_answer": "2006",
      "incorrect_answers": ["2007", "2004", "2005"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "In 'Jewelpet Sunshine', what is the song that plays when Kanon and her friends bust out of prison?",
      "correct_answer": "I Don't Want to Miss a Thing",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Eye Of The Tiger", "Born to be Wild", "Ruby Ring"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "In which manga did the '404 Girl' from 4chan originate from?",
      "correct_answer": "Yotsuba&!",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Azumanga Daioh", "Lucky Star", "Clover"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "What is the name of the school in the anime and manga 'Gosick'?",
      "correct_answer": "St. Marguerite",
      "incorrect_answers": ["St. Augustine", "St. Mary", "St. Bernadette"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "Which animation studio animated 'Hidamari Sketch'?",
      "correct_answer": "Shaft",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Trigger", "Kyoto Animation", "Production I.G"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "Which animation studio animated 'To Love-Ru'?",
      "correct_answer": "Xebec",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Trigger", "Sunrise", "Kyoto Animation"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "Which animation studio animated 'Psycho Pass'?",
      "correct_answer": "Production I.G",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Kyoto Animation", "Shaft", "Trigger"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "Which animation studio produced the anime adaptation of 'xxxHolic'?",
      "correct_answer": "Production I.G",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Sunrise", "Xebec", "Kyoto Animation"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "Which animation studio produced 'Log Horizon'?",
      "correct_answer": "Satelite",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Sunrise", "Xebec", "Production I.G"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "Which animation studio produced 'Sword Art Online'?",
      "correct_answer": "A-1 Pictures",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Production I.G", "Silver Link", "Kyoto Animation"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "Which studio animated Afro Samurai?",
      "correct_answer": "Gonzo",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Kyoto Animation", "xebec", "Production I.G"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "In the Overlord Anime who was Cocytus made by?",
      "correct_answer": "Warrior Takemikazuchi",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Peroroncino",
        "Ulbert Alain Odle",
        "Bukubukuchagama"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "Who was the Author of the manga Uzumaki?",
      "correct_answer": "Junji Ito",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "\tNoboru Takahashi",
        "Akira Toriyama",
        "Masashi Kishimoto"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "Who was the Author of the manga Monster Hunter Orage?",
      "correct_answer": "Hiro Mashima",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Shin Yamamoto", "Keiichi Hikami", "Hirohiko Araki"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "Who is the horror manga artist who made Uzumaki?",
      "correct_answer": "Junji Ito",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Kazuo Umezu", "Shintaro Kago", "Sui Ishida"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "In the first episode of Yu-Gi-Oh: Duel Monsters, what book is Seto Kaiba seen reading at Domino High School?",
      "correct_answer": "Thus Spoke Zarathustra",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Beyond Good and Evil",
        "The Republic",
        "Meditations"
      ]
    }
  ]
}
